<namespaces>
  <namespace name="ILNumerics">
    The ILNumerics namespace provides the main datatypes to be
    used inside the library. At this time those are the main generic array type ILArray<![CDATA[<>]]>
    and the derived types ILCell and ILLogicalArray. The former is a simple alias for
    ILArray<![CDATA[<object>]]>. ILLogicalArray is to be used for boolean operations.
    Also the namespace provides 2 complex datatypes: complex and fcomplex, which extends the
    system's base value types for numerical mathematics on complex floating point base. Those
    base value types may as well be used as inner (generic) types for all ILArray<![CDATA[<>]]>'s.
    Some operations of ILNumerics.Net return a complex Array even on real input arrays. Therefore you
    may want to make yourself familiar with those types also.
  </namespace>
  <namespace name="ILNumerics.Algorithms">
    The ILNumerics.Algorithms namespace provides classes with more complex and/or long running algorithms to be utilized with ILArray<![CDATA[<>]]>'s.
    All algorithms derive from ILAlgorithm class. Therefore ILAlgorithms are capable of informing the host application of special events. Those events may be fired from
    inside of all ILAlgorithms before, during and after processing. A state is associated  with each ILAlgorithm throughout it's livetime. The state is one out the values of
    ILAlgorithmRunningState enum. ILAlgorithms will be started by the public (overloaded) member Run(). The algorithm should inform the host application about its state from 
    time to time, in order to deliver progress information and to query the state of a pending cancelation. Therefore the host application will have the chance to set a flag in 
    the ILAlgorithmEventArgs in order to trigger the cancelation. <br/> ILAlgorithms are proceeding synchronously in general. The host application is responsible for starting 
    a ILAlgorithm in a background thread (e.g. by use of a BackgroundWorker class) and to marshall the event arguments between the threads if necessary. 
  </namespace>
  <namespace name="ILNumerics.BuiltInFunctions">     
		The ILNumerics.BuiltInFunctions namespace provides all built in
		functions for all datatypes derived from ILBaseArray. Those includes all basic math operations
		on ILArray<![CDATA[<>]]> types as well as some extensions to systems value types.
		All functions found inside this namespace are excecuted synchronously. I.e. they are expected to
		excecute in "short time". In contrast to that: see ILAlgorithm/ ILScript, which excecute synchronously also but are 
    better prepared to be taken out into a seperate thread.
	</namespace>
</namespaces>
